Mechanical engineers have changed the world.
机械工程师改变了世界。
You could even say: the course of history.
你甚至可以说：历史的进程。
Not just once but countless times.
不只是一次，而是无数次。
Because they’ve identified problems that were holding humanity back, and they solved them.
因为他们发现了阻碍人类前进的问题，并解决了这些问题。
Things were too big and heavy to move. Travel was too difficult.
东西太大太重，无法移动。旅行太难了。
Distances too far. Our bodies were too weak.
距离太远。我们的身体太虚弱了。
If you can think of an invention that revolutionized the way people live, odds are it was created by mechanical engineers.
如果你能想到一项彻底改变人们生活方式的发明，那么它很可能是由机械工程师创造的。
And I don’t think I’m being biased.
我不认为我有偏见。
Theirs is the field of engineering that focuses on the design, construction, operation, and maintenance of machines and mechanical systems – pretty much anything that moves.
他们的工程领域专注于机器和机械系统的设计、建造、操作和维护——几乎任何移动的东西。
And since the beginning, mechanical engineering has faced a great many challenges, and solved a lot of problems.
从一开始，机械工程就面临着很多挑战，解决了很多问题。
The examples are too many to count, but consider things like the steam engine, airplanes, robots, and biomechanical suits.
例子太多了，数不胜数，但想想蒸汽机、飞机、机器人和生物力学套装。
The engineers behind all of these devices were able to find solutions to big problems.
所有这些设备背后的工程师都能够找到解决大问题的方法。
And of course, they faced difficulties along the way.
当然，他们一路上遇到了困难。
But great efforts almost always do.
但伟大的努力几乎总是如此。
[Theme Music]
[主题音乐]
Back in the day, if you wanted to get somewhere, you would have had two options: your own two feet or a horse.
过去，如果你想去某个地方，你有两种选择：你自己的两只脚或一匹马。
And if you wanted to take a heavy load with you, you needed a carriage. Wheels.
如果你想随身携带重物，你需要一辆马车。车轮。
The invention of the wheel is one of the oldest roots of mechanical engineering, along with all of the simple tools that went into building the carriage itself.
车轮的发明是机械工程最古老的根源之一，以及制造马车本身的所有简单工具。
If we include the simple levers that were used to open gates and bring down bridges, we’d have a great, but primitive, base of early mechanical engineering.
如果我们包括用于打开大门和拆除桥梁的简单杠杆，我们将拥有早期机械工程的一个伟大但原始的基础。
But horse-drawn carriages aren’t very fast.
但是马车不是很快。
A horse needs rest and food, so it would be generous to say you could cover 80 kilometers a day.
一匹马需要休息和食物，所以说你每天可以走 80 公里是慷慨的。
This gave the engineers of the past a problem.
这给过去的工程师带来了一个问题。
As the world opened up, it became more important to cover distances in less time, and horses just weren't cutting it.
随着世界的开放，在更短的时间内完成距离变得越来越重要，而马只是没有削减它。
They needed something faster.
他们需要更快的东西。
They needed an engine.
他们需要一个引擎。
Making its first appearance in the early 18th century, the steam engine marked a major turning point in the development of modern mechanical engineering.
蒸汽机于18世纪初首次出现，标志着现代机械工程发展的重大转折点。
It was proposed that a steam engine could do the work of ten, fifteen, or even twenty horses!
有人提出，一台蒸汽机可以做十匹、十五匹甚至二十匹马的工作！
And you wouldn’t need to bother with any hay...or manure.
而且你不需要为任何干草而烦恼...或粪便。
This brings us to Thomas Newcomen, the British inventor who developed the first successful steam engine with a piston in 1712.
这让我们想到了英国发明家托马斯·纽科门（Thomas Newcomen），他在1712年开发了第一台成功的带活塞的蒸汽机。
In his design, atmospheric pressure pushed the piston down, after the condensation of steam had created a vacuum in the cylinder.
在他的设计中，在蒸汽冷凝在气缸中产生真空后，大气压力将活塞向下推。
Its original use was to draw water out of the Cornish tin mines, after Newcomen found how expensive it was to use horses to pump the water.
它最初的用途是从康沃尔锡矿中抽水，因为纽科曼发现使用马抽水是多么昂贵。
Then along came the Scottish inventor James Watt.
然后是苏格兰发明家詹姆斯·瓦特。
In 1763, while repairing one of Newcomen’s engines,
1763年，在修理纽科门的一台发动机时，
Watt realized that about three quarters of the energy from the steam was going to waste, used only to heat the chamber of the engine.
瓦特意识到，大约四分之三的蒸汽能量将被浪费，仅用于加热发动机的腔室。
His solution was to have a separate condenser.
他的解决方案是有一个单独的冷凝器。
The steam would then be condensed in a chamber separate from the piston chamber, so that the condensed steam didn't go to waste.
然后，蒸汽将在与活塞室分开的腔室中冷凝，这样冷凝的蒸汽就不会浪费。
Keeping the two processes separate allowed for continued rotary motion, which was really important,
将两个过程分开允许继续旋转运动，这非常重要，
because it allowed for a more consistent source of power.
因为它允许更一致的电源。
Watt’s invention came to be widely used to run machines in the factories that drove the Industrial Revolution.
瓦特的发明被广泛用于推动工业革命的工厂机器的运行。
Watt went on to be the first engineer to be commemorated in Westminster Abbey, with a large, white marble statue erected in his memory.
瓦特继续成为威斯敏斯特教堂纪念的第一位工程师，为纪念他竖立了一座巨大的白色大理石雕像。
He also had his last name recognized as a unit of power, which is perhaps one of the highest honors that an engineer can get.
他的姓氏也被公认为权力单位，这也许是工程师可以获得的最高荣誉之一。
But steam engines really came into their own, especially in the realm of transportation, in the locomotives of the 19th century.
但是蒸汽机真正进入了自己的领域，尤其是在运输领域，在 19 世纪的机车中。
George and Robert Stephenson, an English father-son duo, are famous for their early steam locomotive, which they called, aptly enough, “Locomotion.”
乔治和罗伯特·斯蒂芬森是一对英国父子，他们以早期的蒸汽机车而闻名，他们恰如其分地称之为“机车运动”。
In 1825, it became the first public passenger train, carrying 450 people at 24 kilometers per hour.
1825年，它成为第一列公共客运列车，以每小时24公里的速度运送450人。
Quite a bit faster than a horse!
比马快不少！
But while wheeled vehicles allowed people to travel more quickly on land, transportation was still limited by bodies of water and rough, mountainous terrain.
但是，虽然轮式车辆使人们可以在陆地上更快地旅行，但交通仍然受到水体和崎岖山区地形的限制。
If engineers could figure out a way to get people to fly, all of that could be avoided!
如果工程师能找到一种方法让人们飞行，所有这些都可以避免！
This problem-solving led to the invention of aircraft.
这个问题的解决导致了飞机的发明。
The first powered aircraft to take flight was the Wright Flyer in 1903, which was designed by Wilbur and Orville Wright and used a 12-horsepower gas engine.
第一架飞行的动力飞机是1903年的莱特飞行器，它由威尔伯和奥维尔赖特设计，使用12马力的燃气发动机。
Orville flew the Wright Flyer on its maiden voyage, traveling 36 meters in 12 seconds.
奥维尔驾驶莱特飞行器进行处女航，在12秒内飞行了36米。
But the best flight of the day belonged to Wilbur, who traveled over 255 meters in 59 seconds,
但当天最好的飞行属于威尔伯，他在 255 秒内飞行了 59 米，
or a speed of about 15 kilometers an hour, earning him some serious bragging rights.
或者时速约15公里，为他赢得了一些严重的吹牛权。
Soon after the Wright brothers’ accomplishment, World War I sparked a burst of aircraft innovation.
莱特兄弟取得成就后不久，第一次世界大战引发了飞机创新的爆发。
Engineers began using metal in the structures of the airplanes, and better engines, allowing them to reach higher speeds and altitudes.
工程师们开始在飞机的结构中使用金属和更好的发动机，使它们能够达到更高的速度和高度。
Then, in 1930, Sir Frank Whittle obtained his first patent for a turbo-jet engine.
然后，在1930年，弗兰克·惠特尔爵士获得了他的第一个涡轮喷气发动机专利。
But it wasn’t until the outbreak of World War II that the British government had a compelling reason to support his work.
但直到第二次世界大战爆发，英国政府才有令人信服的理由支持他的工作。
By 1941, Whittle’s engine featured a multistage compressor, a combustion chamber, a single turbine, and a nozzle –
到 1941 年，惠特尔的发动机具有多级压缩机、燃烧室、单涡轮和喷嘴——
which was a big improvement, since previous engine designs only had an internal-combustion engine and a propeller.
这是一个很大的改进，因为以前的发动机设计只有内燃机和螺旋桨。
Jet engines outperformed the older designs, flying farther, faster, and cheaper too.
喷气发动机的性能优于旧设计，飞得更远、更快、更便宜。
These advances ultimately made commercial air travel possible, and soon people were traveling where once only the birds had ruled.
这些进步最终使商业航空旅行成为可能，很快人们开始在曾经只有鸟类统治的地方旅行。
But mechanical engineering doesn’t stop in the air!
但机械工程并不止于此！
Beyond planes, we’ve sent satellites into orbit, astronauts to the moon, and spacecraft carrying rovers all the way to Mars.
除了飞机之外，我们还将卫星送入轨道，将宇航员送上月球，并将载着漫游车一路送往火星的航天器。
The aerospace side of engineering actually arose from the mechanical field.
工程的航空航天方面实际上源于机械领域。
And much of what has allowed us to build these machines that move us is another big part of the mechanical engineering field: robotics.
而让我们能够制造这些移动我们的机器的大部分原因是机械工程领域的另一个重要部分：机器人技术。
For most of industrial history, humans have been at the center of our workforce.
在工业历史的大部分时间里，人类一直是我们劳动力的中心。
But humans have their limits.
但人类有其局限性。
Some things are too big and too awkward to move, while other processes needed a finer precision than the human hand allows.
有些东西太大，太笨拙而无法移动，而其他过程需要比人手允许的更精细的精度。
Industrial environments are also often uncomfortable and sometimes even dangerous.
工业环境也经常不舒服，有时甚至是危险的。
And that’s where robots and automation come in.
这就是机器人和自动化的用武之地。
The first industrial robot, called Unimate, appeared around 1960.
第一个工业机器人，称为Unimate，出现在1960年左右。
It was designed by American inventor George Devol, Jr., who worked with engineer and entrepreneur Joseph Engelberger to get it into factories.
它是由美国发明家小乔治·德沃尔（George Devol， Jr.）设计的，他与工程师兼企业家约瑟夫·恩格尔伯格（Joseph Engelberger）合作，将其带入工厂。
Unimate robots had up to six fully programmable axes of motion and could handle parts weighing up to around 225 kilograms at high speeds.
Unimate机器人具有多达六个完全可编程的运动轴，可以高速处理重达约225公斤的零件。
They soon joined the assembly line at a General Motors plant, where they took die castings from machines and welded them onto auto bodies.
他们很快加入了通用汽车工厂的装配线，在那里他们从机器上取压铸件并将它们焊接到车身上。
Since then, robots have gone beyond manufacturing, showing up in our homes to clean the floors, and even hospitals to perform surgeries.
从那时起，机器人已经超越了制造业，出现在我们的家中清洁地板，甚至出现在医院进行手术。
But as their applications get more advanced, engineers have more and more factors to consider.
但随着他们的应用程序变得越来越先进，工程师需要考虑的因素越来越多。
They need to worry about how well robots sense their surroundings, how they move and manipulate their environments, and much more.
他们需要担心机器人如何感知周围环境，如何移动和操纵环境等等。
It’s possible one day that we’ll have robots in many of the places you could imagine a human working.
有朝一日，我们有可能在许多你能想象到人类工作的地方都有机器人。
I mean, we’re seeing that now.
我的意思是，我们现在看到了这一点。
And speaking of humans, you can think of the human body as just a super complex mechanical system of its own, made of links and connecting joints.
说到人类，你可以把人体想象成一个超级复杂的机械系统，由链接和连接关节组成。
And this is where biomechanics comes in.
这就是生物力学的用武之地。
Engineers need to take into account the stress, load, and impact that our bodies can withstand, and apply it to machines that are modeled on us.
工程师需要考虑我们的身体可以承受的压力、负载和冲击，并将其应用于以我们为模型的机器。
Advanced biomechanics is one of the newest divisions of mechanical engineering.
高级生物力学是机械工程的最新部门之一。
From it, we’re already seeing the beginnings of exoskeleton-suits, limbs that move like their biological counterparts, and other robotic implants.
从中，我们已经看到了外骨骼套装的开始，像生物一样移动的肢体，以及其他机器人植入物。
One of the more impressive projects is the Berkeley Lower Extremity Exoskeleton.
其中一个更令人印象深刻的项目是伯克利下肢外骨骼。
Funded by the Defense Advanced Research Project Agency in 2000,
2000年由国防高级研究计划局资助，
this device is designed to provide mechanical support to allow nearly anyone to carry larger, heavier loads than they could ever lift on their own.
该设备旨在提供机械支撑，使几乎任何人都可以承载比他们自己举起的更大，更重的负载。
The ability to carry heavy loads is often a problem for soldiers and disaster relief workers, so finding a solution to this is pretty important.
对于士兵和救灾人员来说，承载重物的能力通常是一个问题，因此找到解决方案非常重要。
But the problems are many.
但问题很多。
For one thing, power sources for exo-suits are often too heavy or cumbersome.
首先，外星人套装的电源通常太重或太笨重。
But the BLEEX, as it’s called, overcomes this by using a small hybrid power source
但是所谓的BLEEX通过使用小型混合动力源来克服这一点。
that delivers hydraulic power for the suit’s locomotion and electrical power for its computer.
这为西装的运动提供液压动力，为其计算机提供电力。
The first prototype was recently introduced, consisting of two powered, anthropomorphic legs, a power unit, and a backpack-like frame.
最近推出了第一个原型，由两个动力的拟人化腿、一个动力装置和一个类似背包的框架组成。
Using the frame, a person can carry a heavy load, but only have it feel like a few pounds.
使用框架，一个人可以承载重物，但只能感觉像几磅。
In similar fashion, Berkeley is also behind the Austin project, which aims to develop exoskeleton systems for people with mobility disorders.
同样，伯克利也是奥斯汀项目的幕后推手，该项目旨在为行动障碍患者开发外骨骼系统。
So it’s almost as if we’ve gone full circle, from the inventors who developed the first steam engine to replace the horse,
因此，从开发第一台蒸汽机取代马的发明家开始，我们几乎就像走了一圈，
to the biomechanical engineers who are using robotics to simulate the most basic means of transportation: walking.
感谢生物力学工程师，他们正在使用机器人技术来模拟最基本的交通工具：步行。
Those are some of the very big problems that mechanical engineers have managed to solve.
这些是机械工程师设法解决的一些非常大的问题。
And when it comes to the problems that we still face today – from driving in traffic to getting food and water to remote areas –
当谈到我们今天仍然面临的问题时——从交通拥堵到向偏远地区提供食物和水——
you can bet that mechanical engineers will be there to tackle them.
您可以打赌机械工程师会在那里解决这些问题。
So today we learned all about many different areas of mechanical engineering, beginning with the steam engine.
所以今天我们学习了机械工程的许多不同领域，从蒸汽机开始。
We then moved on to aircraft and the work behind them.
然后我们转向飞机及其背后的工作。
And we finished by going into the more modern areas of robotics and biomechanics.
最后，我们进入了机器人和生物力学等更现代的领域。
In the next episode we’ll explore electrical engineering, its history, and the work that electrical engineers do.
在下一集中，我们将探讨电气工程、其历史以及电气工程师所做的工作。
Thanks for watching and I’ll see you then.
谢谢你的收看，到时候见。
Crash Course Engineering is produced in association with PBS Digital Studios.
速成课程工程是与PBS Digital Studios联合制作的。
You can head over to their channel to check out a playlist of their latest amazing shows,
您可以前往他们的频道查看他们最新精彩节目的播放列表，
like PBS Space Time, Above the Noise, and Physics Girl.
比如PBS时空，在噪音之上，和物理女孩。
Crash Course is a Complexly production and this episode of was filmed in the Doctor Cheryl C. Kinney Studio with the help of these wonderful people.
速成课程是一个复杂的制作，这一集是在这些优秀的人的帮助下在谢丽尔·C·金尼博士工作室拍摄的。
And our amazing graphics team is Thought Cafe.
我们令人惊叹的图形团队是思想咖啡馆。